13deals.com 2016-05-06

# 13 Deals - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

13 Deals is a Jammin' Butter property.

This Privacy Policy tells you how we collect information when you visit 13 Deals, or if you purchase a product from us. 

At 13 Deals, we understand the importance of your personal information. We ensure that we comply with this obligation, to you (our valued customers). 

When you submit information to 13 Deals by creating an account, purchasing one of our products, or by sending us an email, we collect that information and use it for the purposes of providing you with information or advice about our goods and/or services, and for processing an order by you for our goods and/or services. Specifically, we require your name, street address, email address, phone number and method of payment details in order to complete an order for said goods and/or services. 

We shall only disclose your personal information to third parties where the disclosure is necessary and directly related to the purposes set out above - such as our financial institution to process your order. _**We shall not give our customer lists to third parties for promotions independent of 13 Deals. You do not have to provide us with the information requested; however, we will be unable to process your order should you be unwilling to do so.**_. 

13 Deals relies on word-of-mouth of customers and friends to let it be known about our total awesomeness. To keep you up-to-date on new products and special deals/promotions, we do send occasional emails about promotions and newly listed items. In accordance with the CAN-SPAM Act 2003, we shall only send you emails with your prior consent and shall be happy to remove you from our mailing list should you no longer wish to receive our promotional information. To remove yourself, please go here and enter in your email address.

[Back to top]

All products listed on www.13Deals.com are described to the best of our abilities, and the specifications reflect the information that has been provided to us. All care is taken to ensure this information is correct, but we cannot eliminate the possibility of human error. Should such an error occur, please let us know (that way we can make all things right with the world). You can do so here. [Back to top]

The descriptions of our products are the copyright property of 13 Deals, and specifically you may not use that description as the description of the product should you choose to re-sell the items elsewhere (we know you guys are clever and are more than capable of coming up with your own material). [Back to top]

All orders are prepaid. It is our policy to bill at the point of sale. If your order becomes backordered for longer than 30 days, we will credit your original payment method in full. All orders must be paid for in US Dollars (and are priced as such). Please note that we do not store your credit card information on our server, unless you choose otherwise. [Back to top]

The cost of shipping is clearly indicated for each product ordered, and is included in the invoice total. Orders are generally processed within 72 hours and shipped within 10 days of purchase (unless otherwise stated). We cannot be held responsible for delays brought about by the Postal System, Courier Service Delays, the weather, etc. For more information regarding our shipping policies, please feel free to view our shipping policy in full here. [Back to top]

To enter our sweepstakes or giveaway, please mail postcard to:

Jammin' Butter - Sweepstakes  
Attn: Casey Booyinga  
168 Roweland Drive  
Johnson City, TN 37601

Please include first name, last name, date of birth and email address. One postcard equals one entry. You can enter as many times as you want.

Our way of saying thanks for shopping with 13Deal.com today! Your purchase of $4.99 or more will include a 6 month (6 issues) subscription to Better Homes and Gardens Magazine. Don't worry, NO STRINGS ATTACHED, NO BILL, NO AUTO-RENEWAL! We know you must be thinking... "really?!?!". Yes, really! But come on, you shop with 13Deals.com, so you should be used to insanely good deals. Oh, and if you already have an existing subscription to Better Homes and Gardens, your subscription will simply be extended for an additional 6 months. Again, NO ADDITIONAL COST TO YOU WHATSOEVER. If for some reason you don't want it, although even if YOU won't read it, give it to someone what will, you can simply say no thank you by using coupon code NOMAGMARCHAPRIL during checkout. 

FULL OFFER AND REFUND DETAILS:   
The magazine offer is valid for U.S subscribers only. Please allow 6-8 weeks for the delivery of your first issue of Better Homes and Gardens magazine. If you have an existing subscription to Better Homes and Gardens, your subscription will be extended for an additional 6 months. Each magazine is valued at $4. If you would like a refund for this offer of a magazine subscription, please print out your email receipt and mail within 30 days to the following address to receive a cash allowance for its stated value: Better Homes and Gardens Promotion, 1151 Cleveland St. Clearwater, FL 33755. 

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, or subscribe to our newsletter.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
 _(Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)_
  * To improve our website  
 _(We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)_
  * To improve customer service  
 _(Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)_
  * To process transactions  
 _(Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)_
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails  
 _(The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.)_

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and keep track of advertisements.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'My Account' page.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on 5/17/2013.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information on our contact page

[Back to top]

Please note that 13 Deals and/or Jammin' Butter may revise these terms at any time. Use of this website is subject to the revised terms. This Privacy Policy was last revised on September 18, 2013.
